{
    "id": "2d2fb0cc8fde48718f24c07e16dd5b57",
    "title": "Gap Fills",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I prefer …………………. to riding.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "walk",
                "to walk",
                "walking"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She enjoys …………………",
            "description": "Enjoy is followed by a gerund. ",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "to read",
                "reading"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not used to ………………… late.",
            "description": "When to is a preposition, it is followed by an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "working"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you mind my ………………….. here?",
            "description": "Ing forms are used after do you mind and would you mind?",
            "answers": [
                "sit",
                "to sit",
                "sitting"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is not used to …………………. hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "working"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I still remember ………………….. butterflies when I was young.",
            "description": "Remember is followed by an ing form when the reference is to the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "to chase",
                "chasing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Little girls enjoy ……………………. with dolls.",
            "description": "Enjoy is followed by an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to play",
                "playing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind ………………….. a little?",
            "description": "Ing forms are used after do you mind and would you mind.",
            "answers": [
                "to move",
                "moving"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I forgot …………………… the letter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "posting",
                "to post",
                "to posting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is time he …………………..",
            "description": "A past tense is used after it is time with a present meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "leave",
                "leaving"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is not easy …………………. over the wall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "jumping",
                "to jump"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I …………………. taller.",
            "description": "The past tense is used with a present meaning after I wish. Were is preferred to was in this structure. ",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "were",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}